aryanict.net 2013-01-17

# Privacy Policy - ARYAN ICT Solutions

Our privacy policy is displayed below. This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which AryanIct collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of her websites. **By becoming a customer you acknowledge to have read this privacy policy and agree to it**.

### Effective January 1, 2011

The use of services from AryanIct [hereafter referred to as "Aryanict.com"] constitutes agreement to these terms. You may view our Terms of Service here.

### Introduction

We are committed to protecting any data that we collect concerning you. By using our services you agree to the use of the data that we collect in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### We are committed to protecting your privacy

We collect the minimum amount of information about you that is commensurate with providing you with a satisfactory service. This Policy indicates the type of processes that may result in data being collected about you. Your use of this website gives us the right to collect that information.

Aryanict.com complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. The company has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view the company certification, please visit [ http://www.export.gov/safeharbor](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor)

### Information Collected

We may collect any or all of the information that you give us depending on the type of transaction you enter into, including your name, address, telephone number, fax number and email address, together with data about your use of the website. Other information that may be needed from time to time to process a request may also be collected as indicated on the website.

### Information Use

We use the information collected primarily to process the task for which you visited the website. All reasonable precautions are taken to prevent unauthorized access to this information. This safeguard may require you to provide additional forms of identity should you wish to obtain information about your account details. Aryanict.com may email its monthly newsletter to the primary contact e-mail on file, but customers are able to opt out of this newsletter at any time.

### Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer our site and servers, track access, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. It is possible that personal information about a customer may be included in the log files due to the normal functions of IP addresses and Web browsing.

### Cookies

Your Internet browser has the in-built facility for storing small text files - "cookies" - that hold information which allows a website to recognize your account. We use cookies to save your preferences and login information, and provide personalized functionality. You can reject cookies by changing your browser settings, but be aware that this will disable some of the functionality on the AryanIct's website. More information about cookies can be found at [ http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie).

### Disclosing Information

We do not disclose any personal information obtained about you from this website to third parties. We may use the information to keep in contact with you and inform you of developments associated with our business. You will be given the opportunity to remove yourself from any mailing list or similar device. If at any time in the future we should wish to disclose information collected on this website to any third party, it would only be with your knowledge and consent. 

We may from time to time provide information of a general nature to third parties - for example, the number of individuals visiting our website or completing a registration form, but we will not use any information that could identify those individuals.

### Correcting/Updating Personal Information

If a customer's personally identifiable information changes, or if a customer no longer desires our services, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that customer's personal data in our records. In most cases, this can be achieved via our billing system at [ http://www.aryanict.com/hub/](http://www.aryanict.com/hub/). Otherwise, please contact us at [sales@aryanict.com](mailto:sales@aryanict.com)

**Opt Out & Modifications** By default, customers do receive any voluntary system updates, such as the newsletters, invoices, and mailings. Any customer who voluntarily receives these updates may unsubscribe at any time. Customers may not opt out of possibly receiving important system notifications, in the rare event that such notification would be necessary.

**Security** AryanIct.com uses technical security measures to prevent the loss, misuse, alternation or unauthorized disclosure of information under our control. AryanIct.com uses security measures including and not limited to: physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### Data and Information Submitted to Another Person or Entity on Our Network

As mentioned above, AryanIct.com collects certain data and confidential information from customers relating to our web site hosting and domain registration services, and this Privacy Policy applies only to that data and confidential information submitted to us. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, nor does AryanIct.com certify EU Safe Harbor compliance regarding, data or confidential information that is submitted to another person or entity for whom AryanIct.com may provide hosting or domain name registration services, but regarding which we exercise no authority or control. An independent evaluation of that person or entity's own privacy policy and EU Safe Harbor compliance should be made before submitting data or confidential information to them.

### Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement

We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about Users upon valid request by government or law officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including without limitation subpoenas), to protect your property and rights, or the property and rights of a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or stop activity we consider illegal or unethical.

### Changes to this Policy

Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be placed here and will supersede this version of our Policy. We will take reasonable steps to draw your attention to any changes in our Policy. However, to be on the safe side, we suggest that you read this document each time you use the website to ensure that it still meets with your approval. 

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, or if you want to know what information we have collected about you, please email us at [ support@aryanict.com](mailto:support@aryanict.com). You can also correct any factual errors in that information or require us to remove your details from any list under our control. You can also email us at [support@aryanict.com](mailto:support@aryanict.com).

|  |
